justplay.co.za 2012-06-15

# Online Competition Privacy Policy - View Justplay's Competition Privacy Policy

JustPlay Privacy Policy

Last updated: 2012

Digital Activators cc owns and operates JustPlay - a South African online competition website (http://www.justplay.co.za/Default.aspx) that is governed by the Privacy Policy Statement described below as well as the JustPlay Terms and Conditions Statement. 

Your Privacy   
JustPlay is 100% committed to protecting your privacy. JustPlay uses the information collected to enable you to enjoy the prize draws on the website, to provide support for our product and - with your express consent - to support sponsor promotions and market research. 

What information does JustPlay collect and How is this information used?   
When you register with us, we ask for your name, email address, mobile number, prize preference categories, birth date and gender. We use this information to tailor your online experience and to manage the prize draws. We use email addresses to send out weekly newsletters as well as to notify winners to let them know they have won a prize. We ask winners to show us proof of who they are (through their birthdates and Gender) to ensure we are delivering the prize to the right person. We use the mobile numbers provided in order to contact the winner and for prize delivery. Prize preference categories are used in order to ensure we serve the relevant questionnaires to you, giving you optimal enjoyment of our services.

When you complete sponsor questionnaires as part of your prize draw entry, you may voluntarily choose (throughout a questionnaire and at the end of a questionnaire) \- but are not obliged in any way - to provide information about your lifestyle as well as your preferences to participate in sponsor promotions or market research. It is important to note that you will be entered into a prize draw whether or not you choose/ consent to give your information to or consent to be contacted by the sponsor. 

Only if you consent to sharing information with sponsors, may the sponsors use this information to provide you with product or service related offers, and/or only if you consent to hearing from the sponsor can they aggregate the information for the purposes of market research. Information is only sent to sponsor of the questionnaires should you consent to this. 

Option to discontinue services or direct communication from us   
Should you at any point wish to unsubscribe from our services or discontinue direct communication please either e-mail us on [info@justplay.co.za](mailto:info@justplay.co.za) OR follow online process described here. You simply click on My Justplay (once signed in) and: 

  * **To Cancel your membership or unsubscribe from our website** – Click on My profile on your My Justplay. Click on my membership on the left hand side and click cancel account button on the right. 
  * **To unsubscribe from newsletters** \- Click on newsletters under My activity. Under my newsletters there is a tick box saying I want to receive JustPlay newsletters. Kindly click on the tick-box to un-tick and we will stop sending newsletters to you.

Will JustPlay disclose the information it collects to third parties?   
In order to enter a prize draw on JustPlay, you complete a questionnaire. Most questionnaires are sponsored by a third party in order to conduct a promotion or market research. By giving a positive response on the sponsor's questionnaire you give permission for JustPlay to share your information with that sponsor/client in order for the sponsor/client to contact you or send you an offer: information about products and/or services that may be of interest to you. You can accept or decline the sponsor's offer on each questionnaire. Should you however sign up from the MSN website (http://howzit.msn.com/), you will be signing up to both JustPlay and MSN. Should you however sign up from any [24.com](http://24.com/) website, you will be signing up to both JustPlay and [24.com](http://24.com/)

How does JustPlay protect member information?   
A Secure Server for collecting personal information is used. The secure server layer [SSL] encrypts all the information you enter before it's transmitted over the internet and sent to us. Furthermore, all of the member data we collect is protected against unauthorised access. 

What about cookies?   
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Whenever you log in to JustPlay we store your unique ID [not your SA ID] and the time you signed in, in an encrypted session cookie on your hard drive. When you log out of JustPlay, these session cookes are expired. The functionality of JustPlay depends upon your browser accepting session cookies.

JustPlay tracks visitors to and on the Just Play website by using referrer tracking and uses click through and open mail tracking when sending emails. 

Your Consent   
By using the JustPlay website (http://www.justplay.co.za/) and or signing up through the MSN website (http://howzit.msn.com/), you consent to the collection and use of the information as described above by JustPlay. If any changes are made to this privacy policy, an update will be displayed on the website, so that you are always aware of what information is collected, how it is used, and under what circumstances it is disclosed. The "last updated" date at the top and bottom of the Privacy Statement will be revised should any update occur. 

External Sites and Emails   
JustPlay provides links to other sites from our website and our emails. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibility of the linked site and Just Play has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. JustPlay cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise. 

Contact Information and unsubscribe   
If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy or any other term and conditions on the website please contact Just Play By email at support@justplay.co.za.   
Should you wish to unsubscribe from the justplay services please send us your account name and e-mail address so that we can deactivate your account. You can also manually deactivate your account through the following process: 

  * Sign in
  * Click on My Justplay
  * Click on "Update your Account information" under the Personal Settings block on the left of the screen.
  * Click on My Membership at the bottom right
  * Click on Cancel account button on the centre - right of the screen.

Last updated: 2012
